Guide to the Washington Theater Club records, 1952-1983 MS2061
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Production files, 1960-1979; MS2061 Series 1
  - Scripts, Koesis, Robert - Some Winter Games (Staged Reading 7), undated (Box 33, Folder 748)
  - Scripts, Kossow, Goldie - Ms. Anthrope, undated (Box 33, Folder 749)
  - Scripts, Kruger, Mollee C. - Pins and Needles, Musical Play for Children, undated (Box 33, Folder 750)
  - Lawless, Sue - The Bremen Town Musicians - Lyrics by Herb Sufrin, Music by Jay Brower, undated (Box 33, Folder 00751a)
  - Scripts, Leckie, Mary - Image Incorporated, and Other Sketches, undated (Box 33, Folder 00751b)
  - Scripts, Leckie, Mary - Moving Day, undated (Box 34, Folder 752)
  - Scripts, Leckie, Mary - Return of the Runaway (Production 17), undated (Box 34, Folder 753)
  - Scripts, Leckie, Mary - The Sacred Cow, or Charity Begins at Home, undated (Box 34, Folder 754)
  - Scripts, LoBaito, Jaspar A. & Herbert D. Greggs - Ballad of Riverboat Town, A Musical Play, undated (Box 34, Folder 755)
  - Scripts, Lombardy, D. A. - Sangsara, undated (Box 34, Folder 756)
  - Scripts, Macomber, Carol - Friends, undated (Box 34, Folder 757)
  - Scripts, Malloy, Cy - Symphony for Solitude, A Four Art Festival, undated (Box 34, Folder 758)
  - Scripts, Malouf, Karen - Nobody Doesn't Want to Get Married, undated (Box 34, Folder 759)
  - Scripts, Manchester, Joe - The Secret Life of Walter Mitty, A New Musical Based on the Classic Story by James Thurber. Lyrics by Earl Shuman, Music by Leon Carr, undated (Box 34, Folder 760)
  - Scripts, Maness, Larry - A Matter of Degree, undated (Box 34, Folder 761)
  - Scripts, Marlin-Jones, Davey - Brand Station (Staged Reading 4), undated (Box 34, Folder 762)
  - Scripts, Marshall, Howard - The Living End, undated (Box 35, Folder 763)
  - Scripts, Mason, Clifford - Gabriel, The Story of a Slave Rebellion, undated (Box 35, Folder 764)
  - Scripts, Mayer, Heidy & Leah Colker - Sammy the Street Cleaner, An 0peretta for Children. Based on a Story by Heidy Mayer. Music by Leah Colker, undated (Box 35, Folder 765)
  - Scripts, Mee, Charles L., Jr. - The Life of the Party, undated (Box 35, Folder 766)
  - Scripts, Mehta, Xerxes J. - American Antigone, undated (Box 35, Folder 767)
  - Scripts, Miller, Arthur - A View from the Bridge, undated (Box 35, Folder 768)
  - Scripts, Miller, Bruce - Me, undated (Box 35, Folder 769)
  - Scripts, Mitts, Charles-7-The Sky Below, undated (Box 35, Folder 770)
  - Scripts, M Mother, My Father, and Me, undated (Box 35, Folder 771)
  - Scripts, The Naked Man, undated (Box 35, Folder 772)
  - Scripts, Neft, Deborah & Susan Hagedorn - Once upon the National League West, undated (Box 35, Folder 773)
  - Scripts, Oabler, Carl - Countess Frieda (Staged Reading 14), undated (Box 35, Folder 774)
  - Scripts, Oddo, Jasper - Someone's Crying (Staged Reading 15), undated (Box 35, Folder 775)
  - Scripts, O'Donnell, Richard - And Other Caged Birds (Production 52 & Staged Reading 6), undated (Box 35, Folder 776)
  - Scripts, O'Donnell, Richard - Bad Night in Bad Eigen, undated (Box 35, Folder 777)
  - Scripts, O'Donnell, Richard - The Family Room (Staged Reading 3), undated (Box 35, Folder 778)
  - Scripts, Ordway, Sally - Movie, Movie on the Wall, undated (Box 36, Folder 779)
  - Scripts, Osborn, Paul - Point of No Return, undated (Box 36, Folder 780)
  - Scripts, O'Sullivan, R. T. & J. E. Danielsen - Too Pooped to Pope, the Peregrinations of a Discalced Monk, undated (Box 36, Folder 781)
  - Scripts, Panas, Alexander - Emma Z..., undated (Box 36, Folder 782)
  - Scripts, Panas, Alexander - An Evening with Mr. Poe (Staged Reading 13), undated (Box 36, Folder 783)
  - Scripts, Panas, Alexander - The Scene Please, Mr. Tambo, Mr. Bones (Production 50) as Mr. Tambo, Mr. Bones (Staged Reading 5), undated (Box 36, Folder 784)
  - Scripts, Teichmann, Howard & George S. Kaufman - The Solid Gold Cadillac, undated (Box 36, Folder 819)
  - Scripts, Terry, Bob - Paris and Helen, undated (Box 36, Folder 820)
  - Scripts, Thompson, Jay & Marshall Barer & Dean Fuller - Once upon a Mattress. Music by Mary Rodgers, undated (Box 36, Folder 821)
  - Scripts, Thompson, Olean E. - The Hats, undated (Box 36, Folder 822)
  - Scripts, Thompson, Olean E. - She Was So Lovely, undated (Box 36, Folder 823)
  - Scripts, Tillotson, Richard - Diversionary Tactics, undated (Box 36, Folder 824)
  - Scripts Rosofsky, Iris Faye - 1204 (Staged Reading 3), 1968 February 26 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #793
  - Scripts Ryan, Henry Butterfield, Jr. - Number 172 and Its Gallant Crew, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #794
  - Scripts Ryga, George - The Ecstasy of Rita Joe (Production 95), undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #795
  - Scripts Saroyan, William - The Slaughter of the Innocents, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #796
  - Scripts Schisgal, Murray - The Chinese & Dr. Fish (Production 68), undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #797
  - Scripts Schwenger, Robert B. - Potiphar Revisited, 1969 February 24 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Formerly folder #798
  - Scripts Seale, D. - Lady Audley's Secret Adapted from the 1860 Novel by M. E. Braddon. Music by G. Goehring Lyrics by J. Kuntz (Production 78), undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Formerly folder #799
  - Scripts Shaw, George Bernard - The Devil's Disciple, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Formerly folder #800
  - Scripts Shaw, George Bernard - Misalliance, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Formerly folder #801
  - Scripts Shaw, Irwin - By the Old Moulmein Pagoda (Staged Reading 1), 1968 December 04 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Formerly folder #802
  - Scripts Shepard, Sam - Geography of a Horse Dreamer - A Mystery, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Formerly folder #803
  - Scripts Somerfeld, Robert - The Note (Staged Reading 10), undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
    Formerly folder #804
  - Scripts Spewack, Sam & Bella - My 3 Angels, 1954 June (Box 37, Folder 13)
    Formerly folder #805
  - Spewack, Samuel - Under the Sycamore Tree, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Formerly folder #806
  - Scripts Spigelgass, Leonard - A Majority of One, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Formerly folder #807
  - Scripts Spread Eagle (Production 30), undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Formerly folder #808
  - Scripts Spread Eagle Strikes Back (Production 45), undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #809
  - Scripts Stagliano, Vito - Saturn, A Birth in Three Acts, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #810
  - Scripts Starkweather, David - Chamber Comedy (Staged Reading 8), 1969 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #811
  - Scripts St. Clair, Sean - "No", undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #812
  - Scripts Sutton, Dolores - The Web and the Rock Based on Thomas Wolfe (Production 67), undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #813
  - Scripts Sweet, Herb - Musical Numbers, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Formerly folder #814
  - Scripts Sweet, Jeff - Instant Foreplay, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Formerly folder #815
  - Scripts Sweet, Jeff - Spooked, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Formerly folder #816
  - Scripts Taylor, Samuel - The Happy Time, 1951 February (Box 38, Folder 9)
    Formerly folder #817
  - Scripts Taylor, Samuel, with Cornelia Otis Skinner - The Pleasure of His Company, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Formerly folder #818
  - Scripts Teichmann, Howard & George S. Kaufman - The Solid Gold Cadillac, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Formerly folder #819
  - Scripts Terry, Bob - Paris and Helen, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
    Formerly folder #820
  - Scripts Thompson, Jay & Marshall Barer & Dean Fuller - Once Upon a Mattress Music by Mary Rodgers, 1960 July (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Formerly folder #821
  - Scripts Thompson, Olean E. - The Hats, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
    Formerly folder #822
  - Scripts Thompson, Olean E. - She Was So Lovely, undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
    Formerly folder #823
  - Scripts Tillotson, Richard - Diversionary Tactics, undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
    Formerly folder #824
  - Scripts, Turner, Dennis - The Rapists (Production 80), undated (Box 39, Folder 825)
  - Scripts, Udoff, Yale M. - Dust to Dust, an Inevitable Tragedy, undated (Box 39, Folder 826)
  - Scripts, Udoff, Yale M. - The Rose Critic, a Joke, undated (Box 39, Folder 827)
  - Scripts, U o Bett, Time of Vengeance, undated (Box 39, Folder 828)
  - Scripts, Vidal, Gore - Visit to a Small Planet, undated (Box 39, Folder 829)
  - Scripts, Walman Jerome & Kenneth Jerome - Washington Square, A Musical Play, undated (Box 39, Folder 830)
  - Scripts, Wellman, John - Fama Combinatoria: a Pastoral Eclogue for Television, undated (Box 39, Folder 831)
  - Scripts, Wentworth, John B. & Hod Ogden - The Finney Touch, undated (Box 39, Folder 832)
  - Scripts, West, Robert W. - Graffito Bus Blues, undated (Box 39, Folder 833)
  - Scripts, Westheimer, David - My Sweet Charlie (Production 40), undated (Box 39, Folder 834)
  - Scripts, Whelan, Bill - The Philistine ... a Canticle, undated (Box 39, Folder 835)
  - Scripts, Whitney, Arthur - The Lydia Lamont Fan Club Will Please Come to Order, undated (Box 39, Folder 836)
  - Scripts, Wilder, Thornton - The Matchmaker (Production 1), undated (Box 40, Folder 837)
  - Scripts, Wilder, Thornton - Plays for Bleecker Street, undated (Box 40, Folder 838)
  - Scripts, Williams, Tennessee - Streetcar Named Desire (Scene 4 Only), undated (Box 40, Folder 839)
  - Scripts, Wilson, John - No Man's Land (Production 42), undated (Box 40, Folder 840)
  - .Scripts, Wisoff, Milton - Odds & Ends (Production 52), undated (Box 40, Folder 841)
  - Scripts, Wiswell, Thomas Gerard - By the Shattering of Icons, undated (Box 40, Folder 842)
  - Scripts, Wiswell, Thomas Gerard - Darling, Who's That Rocking?, undated (Box 40, Folder 843)
  - Scripts, Wiswell, Thomas Gerard - Over the Candittied Olocicles, undated (Box 40, Folder 844)
  - Scripts, Wittinger, Karl - Do You Know the Milk Way?, undated (Box 40, Folder 845)
  - Scripts, Wolff, Ruth - Armed Love, undated (Box 40, Folder 846)
  - Scripts, Zone of Indifference, undated (Box 40, Folder 847)
  - Script Reading, 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 848)
  - Script Reading, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 849)
  - Script Reading, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 850)
  - Script Reading, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 851)
  - Script Reading A-J, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 852)
  - Script Reading K-Z [1/2], 1968 November 19-1969 December 30 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #853
  - Script Reading K-Z [2/2], 1968 November 19-1969 December 30 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Script Reading A-L [1/2], 1969 December 16-1970 October 26 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #854
  - Script Reading A-L [2/2], 1969 May 19-1970 December 23 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Script Reading M-Z, 1970 January 20-1979 October 08 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #855
  - Production Series - Resumes Index Files, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Formerly Folder #856
  - Resumes - Aaron-Alford, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #857
  - Resumes Algar-Ammon, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #858
  - Resumes Anderson-Aranha, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #859
  - Resumes Arbeit-Axelrod, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #860
  - Resumes Backer-Baltin, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #861
  - Resumes Banick-Barrett, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Formerly folder #862
  - Resumes Barrientez-Bayley, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #863
  - Resumes Beach - Benoit, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #864
  - Resumes Bensal-Bevine, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #865
  - Resumes Bianchi-Bolt, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #866
  - Resumes Bond-Bozick, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #867
  - Resumes Bradbury-Brill, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #868
  - Resumes Brocato-Bryon, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #869
  - Resumes Buchheit-Byrne, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #870
  - Resumes Cadel-Carlson, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #871
  - Resumes Carlton-Cavey, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #872
  - Resumes Cesaitis-Christmas, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #873
  - Resumes Christofferson-Cohn, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #874
  - Resumes Cole-Cooke, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #875
  - Resumes Cooper-Cotten, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #876
  - Resumes Coughlan-Creamer, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #877
  - Resumes Creswell-Cwikowski, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Formerly folder #878
  - Resumes, Dabrowski - Davidson, undated (Box 48, Folder 879)
  - Resumes, Davis - Deaven, undated (Box 48, Folder 880)
  - Resumes, De Baer - Bezseran, undated (Box 48, Folder 881)
  - Resumes, Diaz - Dowdell, undated (Box 48, Folder 882)
  - Resumes, Dowling - Dzundza, undated (Box 48, Folder 883)
  - Resumes, Eagan - Elliott, undated (Box 48, Folder 884)
  - Resumes, Ellis - Everett, undated (Box 49, Folder 885)
  - Resumes, Fahey - Feltman, undated (Box 49, Folder 886)
  - Resumes, Ferguson-Wagstaffe - Flynn, undated (Box 49, Folder 887)
  - Resumes, Fodor - Frazier, undated (Box 49, Folder 888)
  - Resumes, Fredricksen - Funk, undated (Box 49, Folder 889)
  - Resumes, Gabel - Gettleman, undated (Box 49, Folder 890)
  - Resumes, Giannini - Glendinning, undated (Box 49, Folder 891)
  - Resumes, Goble - Greene, undated (Box 50, Folder 892)
  - Resumes, Greenan - Gussman, undated (Box 50, Folder 893)
  - Resumes, Haak - Harpman, undated (Box 50, Folder 894)
  - Resumes, Harrel - Haynes, undated (Box 50, Folder 895)
  - Resumes, Hebert - Hess, undated (Box 50, Folder 896)
  - Resumes, Hessian - Hirsch, undated (Box 51, Folder 897)
  - Resumes, Hobe - Hoover, undated (Box 51, Folder 898)
  - Resumes, Hopkins - Huber, undated (Box 51, Folder 899)
  - Resumes, Huff - Hyslop, undated (Box 51, Folder 900)
  - Resumes, lannicelli - Jerom, undated (Box 51, Folder 901)
  - Resumes, Jochim - Justin, undated (Box 51, Folder 902)
  - Resumes, Kahn - Kelleher, undated (Box 52, Folder 903)
  - Resumes, Kelley - Kirsch, undated (Box 52, Folder 904)
  - Resumes, Kleeman - Kornbluth, undated (Box 52, Folder 905)
  - Resumes, Kornman - Kyle, undated (Box 52, Folder 906)
  - Resumes, Lack - Lathram, undated (Box 52, Folder 907)
  - Resumes, Latter - Lehrman, undated (Box 52, Folder 908)
  - Resumes, Leighton - Lewison, undated (Box 53, Folder 909)
  - Resumes, L'Heureux - Lonergan, undated (Box 53, Folder 910)
  - Resumes, Long - Lytle, undated (Box 53, Folder 911)
  - Resumes, McBroom - McKee, undated (Box 53, Folder 912)
  - Resumes, McKenna - McPherson, undated (Box 53, Folder 913)
  - Resumes, Madeley - Marshall, undated (Box 54, Folder 914)
  - Resumes, Martin - Mazza, undated (Box 54, Folder 915)
  - Resumes, Meacham - Michalski, undated (Box 54, Folder 916)
  - Resumes, Michel - Mogavero, undated (Box 54, Folder 917)
  - Resumes, Molyneaux - Morris, undated (Box 54, Folder 918)
  - Resumes, Morrison - Myles, undated (Box 55, Folder 919)
  - Resumes, Nagel - Nisbet, undated (Box 55, Folder 920)
  - Resumes, Nixon - Nunnery, undated (Box 55, Folder 921)
  - Resumes, Oak - Oyster, undated (Box 55, Folder 922)
  - Resumes, Packard - Parish, undated (Box 55, Folder 923)
  - Resumes, Parker - Payne, undated (Box 55, Folder 924)
  - Resumes, Peacock - Peterson, undated (Box 56, Folder 925)
  - Resumes, Patretti - Pitman, undated (Box 56, Folder 926)
  - Resumes, Place - Poole, undated (Box 56, Folder 927)
  - Resumes, Poppick - Quincy, undated (Box 56, Folder 928)
  - Resumes, Radcliffe - Reinish, undated (Box 56, Folder 929)
  - Resumes, Reis - Risk, undated (Box 56, Folder 930)
  - Resumes, Robbins - Rose, undated (Box 57, Folder 931)
  - Resumes, Rosen - Roulet, undated (Box 57, Folder 932)
  - Resumes, Routh - Ryerson, undated (Box 57, Folder 933)
  - Resumes, Sabin - Savage, undated (Box 57, Folder 934)
  - Resumes, Saxe - Schnitzer, undated (Box 57, Folder 935)
  - Resumes, Schore - Scott, undated (Box 58, Folder 936)
  - Resumes, Scoullar - Shapiro, undated (Box 58, Folder 937)
  - Resumes, Sharp -Silver, undated (Box 58, Folder 938)
  - Resumes, Simkin -Smiley, undated (Box 58, Folder 939)
  - Resumes, Smith -Snyder, undated (Box 58, Folder 940)
  - Resumes, Soares -Squire, undated (Box 58, Folder 941)
  - Resumes, Stahihuth - Stinson, undated (Box 59, Folder 942)
  - Resumes, Stock - Stuart, undated (Box 59, Folder 943)
  - Resumes, Stubbs - Symmons, undated (Box 59, Folder 944)
  - Resumes, Tabbat - Thomson, undated (Box 59, Folder 945)
  - Resumes, Thorny - Townsend, undated (Box 59, Folder 946)
  - Resumes, Trankina - Van Etten, undated (Box 60, Folder 947)
  - Resumes, Van Keuren - Vossen, undated (Box 60, Folder 948)
  - Resumes, Wagoner - Webb, undated (Box 60, Folder 949)
  - Resumes, Webster - Weyte, undated (Box 60, Folder 950)
  - Resumes, Wheeler - Williams, undated (Box 60, Folder 951)
  - Resumes, Williamson - Withers, undated (Box 61, Folder 952)
  - Resumes, Wolf - Wynn, undated (Box 61, Folder 953)
  - Resumes, Yaffee - Zwerling, undated (Box 61, Folder 954)
  - Original Lists 7, undated (Box 62, Folder 954)
  - Special Production 1, On-the-Spot Playmaking, 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 955)
  - Special Production 2, Goodbye Tiger, Guerdon Trueblood, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 956)
  - Special Production 3, Variety - a Vaudeville of Characters, Logan Ramsey, 1961 November 03-11 (Box 63, Folder 957)
  - Special Production 4, A Variety Show, Howard Troupers, 1963 June 08 (Box 63, Folder 958)
  - Special Production 5, Roses, Susan Levine, 1963 June 21-23 (Box 63, Folder 959)
  - Special Production 6, Evening of Chilean Theater: As They Do in Santiago, Barros Grez; Apablaza's Widow, Luco Cruchaga; Little Town, Armando Moock; Mama Rosa, Fernando Debesa; & Requiem for a Sunflower, George Diaz, 1963 October 21 (Box 63, Folder 960)
  - Special Production 7, Matt and the Moron and Madonna, Herbert Lieberman, 1965 July 07-25 (Box 63, Folder 961)
  - Special Production 8, An Evening with Sue and Pugh, Sue Lawless & Ted Pugh. Jan. 9, 1966 June 30-July 10 (Box 63, Folder 962)
  - Special Production 9, A Mythical Tour of Spain - Daniel de Cordoba, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 963)
  - Special Production 10, The Hobbit, Adapted from Tolkien by Patricia Gray, 1970 August 24 (Box 63, Folder 964)
  - Special Production 11, Groove Tube, Vitreous Humor, Inc.-(0 St. Rental), 1971 October 15 (Box 63, Folder 965)
  - Special Production 12, Let There Be Light, Lumia Company. Apr, Circa 1974 (Box 63, Folder 966)
  - Special Production 13, Tambourines to Glory - Langston Hughes. (Presented by McKinley High School), 1974 August 04-05 (Box 63, Folder 967)
  - Special Production 14, An Evening with Lee Strasberg, 1974 November 11 (Box 63, Folder 968)
  - Informals 1, Sunday or Monday Night Informals - Announcements, 1963-1966 (Box 63, Folder 969)
  - Staged Reading 1, The Death of Morris Biederman, Bob Cohen & By the Old Moulmein Pagoda, Irwin Shaw, 1967 December 04 (Box 63, Folder 970)
  - Staged Reading 2, The Saga of Hoo Fasa, Edward de Grazia, 1968 January 15 (Box 63, Folder 971)
  - Staged Reading 3, The Family Room, Richard O'Donnell & Twelve-Oh-Four, Iris Faye Rosofsky, 1968 February 26 (Box 63, Folder 972)
  - Staged Reading 4, Brand Station, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 March 25 (Box 63, Folder 973)
  - Staged Reading 5, The Scene, Please Mr. Tambo, Mr. Bones, Alexander Panas. (postponed from Apr. 8), 1968 April 22 (Box 63, Folder 974)
  - Staged Reading 6, And Other Caged Birds, Richard O'Donnell & Willyum, Philip Staged Balestrino, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 975)
  - Staged Reading 7, Some Winter Games, Richard Koesis, 1969 January 20 (Box 63, Folder 976)
  - Staged Reading 8, Chamber Corned, David Starkweather., 1969 February 24 (Box 63, Folder 977)
  - Staged Reading 9, Odds and Ends, Milton Wisoff & Sleeping Dog Bruce Harrison, 1969 March 31 (Box 63, Folder 978)
  - Staged Reading 10, The Note & The Production Room, Robert Somerfield., 1969 May 05 (Box 63, Folder 979)
  - Staged Reading 11, Miss Harolde to the Dark Tower Came, Lucy Kennedy; You Can't Sell Cornbeef in July & Our Next Luck Contestant Is..., Marvin Himelfarb, 1969 June 15 (Box 63, Folder 980)
  - Staged Reading 12, Red Mountain High, Robert Auletta, 1969 December 01 (Box 63, Folder 981)
  - Staged Reading 13, An Evening with Mr. Poe, Alexander Panas, 1970 January 26 (Box 64, Folder 982)
  - Staged Reading 14, Countess Frieda, Carl Gabler., 1970 February 09 (Box 64, Folder 983)
  - StagedReading 15, Someone's Crying, Jason Oddo. (postponed from Mar.9), 1970 March 16 (Box 64, Folder 984)
  - Staged Reading 16, Popcorn, David Epstein, 1970 April 13 (Box 64, Folder 985)
  - Staged Reading 17, Caged?, Cyril I. Malloy, Jr. & Hank Is My Name, Marvin Himelfarb, 1970 May 18 (Box 64, Folder 986)
  - Staged Reading 18, The Great Chinese Revolution, Anthony Scully, 1970 November 30 (Box 64, Folder 987)
  - Staged Reading 19, Claw Man, Leon Gillen, 1971 February 01 (Box 64, Folder 988)
  - Staged Reading 20, Sleep & Put on Your Potato Jacket, Sam Smiley, 1971 February 22 (Box 64, Folder 989)
  - Staged Reading 21, Clown, Jack Gonzales, 1971 April 12 (Box 64, Folder 990)
  - Staged Reading 22, Out of Sight, David Calicchio, 1971 April 12 (Box 64, Folder 991)
  - Staged Reading 23, The Presentation & Sundays Aren't What They Used to Be & Ladies Day, Marvin Himelfarb, 1971 May 17 (Box 64, Folder 992)
  - Staged Reading 24, The Deadly Delilah, Raleigh Bond, 1971 October 04 (Box 64, Folder 993)
  - Staged Reading 25, "A Little Singing" & "A Little Dancing", Robert Kimmel Smith, 1971 October 18 (Box 64, Folder 994)
  - Staged Reading 26, The Knackers Yard, Johnny Speight, 1971 November 15 (Box 64, Folder 995)
  - Staged Reading 27, Stations, Three One-Act Plays: "Madame Cleo Here, at Your Service", Warren Kliewer; "Carnival Party", Henry B. Ryan; & "Playground", Louis Vuolo, 1971 December 20 (Box 64, Folder 996)
  - Staged Reading 28, Monolith, Jeffrey Thresher, 1972 January 24 (Box 64, Folder 997)
  - Staged Reading 29, The Wizard of Spruce Street, Deborah Lundy, 1972 February 28 (Box 64, Folder 998)
  - Staged Reading 30, Fire on Water, Lucy Kennedy, 1972 April 03 (Box 64, Folder 999)
  - Staged Reading 31, The Night Watchmen, Stratis Karras, translated by Evangelos Voutsinas, 1972 May 01 (Box 64, Folder 1000)
  - Staged Reading 32, Thanksgiving at Aunt Bett 's, Robert Riche, 1972 May 15 (Box 64, Folder 1001)
  - Staged Reading 33, Wild Bill, John Clifford, 1972 June 05 (Box 64, Folder 1002)
  - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 64, Folder 1003)
  - Funding - Box Office, 1969-1970 (Box 64, Folder 1004)
  - Funding - Box Office, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 1005)
  - Theater Chamber Players 1, 1968 June 10 (Box 65, Folder 1006)
  - Theater Chamber Players 2, 1968 December 30 (Box 65, Folder 1007)
  - Theater Chamber Players 3, 1969 February 03 (Box 65, Folder 1008)
  - Theater Chamber Players 4, 1969 April 28 (Box 65, Folder 1009)
  - Theater Chamber Players 5, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 1010)
  - Theater Chamber Players 6, 1969 November 20 (Box 65, Folder 1011)
  - Theater Chamber Players 7, 1969 December 29 (Box 65, Folder 1012)
  - Theater Chamber Players 8, 1970 January 19 (Box 65, Folder 1013)
  - Theater Chamber Players 9, 1970 February 23 (Box 65, Folder 1014)
  - Theater Chamber Players 10, 1970 May 25 (Box 65, Folder 1015)
  - Theater Chamber Players 11, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 1016)
  - Theater Chamber Players 12, 1970 December 14 (Box 65, Folder 1017)
  - Theater Chamber Players 13, 1971 January 16 (Box 65, Folder 1018)
  - Theater Chamber Players 14, 1971 March 01 (Box 65, Folder 1019)
  - Theater Chamber Players 15, 1971 May 03 (Box 65, Folder 1020)